gettingoutside.com 2010-12-29

# Privacy Policy | outdoor, recreation, adventure, fun, kids, family, camping, hiking, backpacking, fishing, travel, vacation

**Privacy Policy**

Effective Date: February 15, 2010

**GettingOutside.com takes your privacy seriously!**

WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS

This policy covers how GettingOutside.com treats personal information that GettingOutside.com collects and receives, including information related to your use of GettingOutside.com products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that GettingOutside.com does not own or control, or to people that GettingOutside.com does not employ or manage. In addition, some companies that GettingOutside.com is related to through Neske LLC have their own, preexisting privacy policies. 

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

GENERAL

GettingOutside.com collects personal information when you register with GettingOutside.com, when you use GettingOutside.com products or services , when you visit GettingOutside.com pages or the pages of certain GettingOutside.com partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes . GettingOutside.com may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

When you register we ask for information like your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. To better serve you and provide you with the most relevant information and user experience we might also ask for your address and information about your profession and financial resources. When you register with GettingOutside.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

GettingOutside.com collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

GettingOutside.com automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address , GettingOutside.com cookie information, the page(s) you request, and the social networking information you record, whether you choose to share it with others or not. 

GettingOutside.com uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, fulfill sweepstakes and incentive programs, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

CHILDREN

GettingOutside.com does not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes without a parent's permission.

GettingOutside.com does not ask a child under age 13 for more personal information, as a condition of participation, than is reasonably necessary to participate in a given activity or promotion. 

INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

GettingOutside.com does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with GettingOutside.com under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help GettingOutside.com communicate with you about offers from GettingOutside.com and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

We have a parent's permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing GettingOutside.com to collect and use their child's information without consenting to GettingOutside.com sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes. 

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of GettingOutside.com's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

We transfer information about you if GettingOutside.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, GettingOutside.com will notify you that information about you has been transferred and has become subject to a different privacy policy.   
GettingOutside.com displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria—for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. 

GettingOutside.com does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

GettingOutside.com advertisers may include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies). 

GettingOutside.com works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

COOKIES

GettingOutside.com may set and access GettingOutside.com cookies on your computer. 

GettingOutside.com lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to GettingOutside.com's cookies.

GettingOutside.com may use web beacons to access GettingOutside.com cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with GettingOutside.com products and services. 

YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES 

GENERAL

You can edit your GettingOutside.com Account Information , including your subscription preferences , at any time. 

New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Subscription preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the GettingOutside.com service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the GettingOutside.com Newsletter, that are considered part of your GettingOutside.com account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. 

You can delete your GettingOutside.com account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Some information might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. (See Terms of Service)

CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. However, no electronic safeguards are perfect. Protect your account passwords and security. Use the site and services at your own risk.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

GettingOutside.com may update this policy. At our discretion, we will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your GettingOutside.com account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at: 

GettingOutside.com (Neske LLC).  
Privacy Policy Issues  
http://www.gettingoutside.com/contact
